A Guide to the Theodore Shedlovsky papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA130
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Artifacts, undated; 16; 0.8 Cubic Feet
  - Name tags and business cards (Box 53)
  - Tiles for Caspary (Box 54)
  - Rolls of unidentified 35mm color/ black & white film (Box 55)
  - A Get Well Poster, [processed but needs to be rehoused once materials are available] (Box 56)
  - World Academy of Art and Science Certificate, [processed but needs to be rehoused once materials are available] (Box 57)